Boyd Hinds Papers
Hartford History Center, Hartford Public Library
Boyd Hinds Papers
1970-1987
Hartford History Center, Hartford Public Library Hartford, Connecticut
Hinds, Boyd
20 linear feet (46 boxes)
Papers of civil rights activist Boyd Hinds, including archival materials of Education/Instruccion. The collection focuses on institutionalized racism as reflected in education, housing and finance policy and practices in the city of Hartford in the 1970-1987 time period as well as Hinds' career as a state representative 1976-1980.
Historical Note
Born in 1939 in raised in a Hartford suburb, Boyd Hinds (1939-1988) graduated Amherst College in 1961. After graduation, he married wife Wendy Hinds, and initially entered an executive training program with the New York Telephone Company. A two-year stint in the navy (1963-1965) confronted Hinds with the disparity between officers and enlisted men, a consciousness he brought with him when he arrived in the city of Hartford in 1970. Hinds taught English at Kingswood School before joining faculty at Westledge School in Simsbury. There he met Ben Dixon and Julia Ramos with whom he would co-found and co-direct Education/Instruccion beginning in 1970. Together, Hinds, Dixon and Ramos conducted research and led initiatives to combat racism within institutional structures, including the real estate, banking and insurance industries. Hinds served as a state representative of Hartford’s 8th Assembly District from 1976 to 1980. After leaving office, he continued his work with Education/Instruccion until his death in 1988.
Scope and Content
The Boyd Hinds Papers reflect a lifelong commitment to civil rights activism in Hartford, Connecticut. This collection contains significant archival materials of Education/Instruccion, a civil rights organization founded in 1970 to work against institutionalized racism in the city of Hartford. Specifically, its members conducted research on discrimination in education, and investigated civil rights abuses in Hartford’s real estate, insurance, and banking industries. The collection includes transcripts and audio tapes from investigations into local market practices such as redlining, and the compliance of Hartford’s realtors with Title VIII of the Civil Rights Act of 1968, better known as the Fair Housing Act. It also includes documentation used in legal challenges to the discrimination they found, and publicity materials the organization used to educate the public about institutional racism. Boyd Hinds served as a state representative of Hartford’s 8th Assembly District from 1976-1980, and the collection includes documentation from his time in office as well.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in three series, topically and chronologically.
Access Restrictions
The records are stored in a restricted area and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
Accruals
The collection is closed. Additional accruals are not expected.
Subject Headings
Personal Names
Hinds, Boyd
Corporate Names
Education/Instruccion
Subjects
Civil rights; Discrimination in education; Discrimination in housing; Discrimination in insurance; Fund raising; Legislators; Political activists
Genre Terms
Audiotapes; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Minutes (administrative records); Pamphlets; Photographs; Transcripts
Contents:
- Series I: Education/Instruccion Administrative Records, Campaign Archives, and Research
  - Box 1 - Redlining Research Materials
    - Redlining – federal regulations
    - Redlining- California regulations
    - Redlining lawsuit vs. regulatory agencies, 1976
    - Redlining - South Shore National Bank, 1976
    - Redlining - South Shore National Bank pamphlets
    - Andy Gold. Report to the state banking commissioner regarding "redlining" and mortgage disclosure, 1977
  - Box 2 - Education/Instruccion – Redlining
    - Education/Instruccion Inc – Redlining Clipping File, 1973-197?
    - “Black City Politics” by Ernest Patterson. Manuscript, 1974
    - Education/Instruccion Inc. appraisal lawsuit, 1975
    - Education/Instruccion Inc. - FHA appraisals and correspondence, 1975
    - Hartford anti-blockbusting ordinance, 1976
    - Reports of declining tax revenue, 1976
    - Bank appraisal investigation press clippings, 1977
    - E/I The Benefits of Exclusionary Zoning Lawsuits, draft, 1977
    - Hartford redlining ordinance, correspondence, meeting notes, etc., 1979
    - Hartford redlining ordinance, 1979
    - Redlining bills
  - Box 3 - Education/Instruccion – Housing
    - HUD files, 1966, 1977
    - Department of Housing - dwelling unit inventories, 1965-1978
    - City housing programs, 1976-1977
    - E/I housing and City of Hartford, 1977
    - Housing letters protesting redlining in public housing
    - Section 8
    - HUD funded projects, Tuscan Homes, 1978
    - Assignment of the Poor to Neighborhoods - analysis of city public housing
    - Leased housing, City of Hartford, notes and correspondence, 1978
    - Neighborhood housing services report
    - CARP vs. Mary B. Eaton and the William Beazley Co., 1979
  - Box 4 - Redlining Research Photographs
    - Photographs of housing (Bloomfield, Hartford, West Hartford)
    - Photographs of housing (Bloomfield, Colchester, East Hartford, Enfield, Hartford, Newington, West Hartford)
    - Redlining - national actions
    - Redlining articles
  - Box 5 - Education/Instruccion 1970- (early articles/exposes)
    - E/I letters to the editor (assorted), 1971-1972
    - E/I “North Hartford Truth” editorials, 1972-1975
    - E/I “North Hartford Truth” editorial clippings
    - E/I Hartford Star articles
    - The Daily Grind, May 1977
    - Newspaper clippings (misc.)
  - Box 6 - Education/Instruccion Ya Basta
    - E/I Project STB – sample questions for interviews/project desc., 1973
    - E/I STB and Dual Housing Project report – binder 1 of 2, 1973
    - E/I STB and Dual Housing Project report – binder 2 of 2, 1973
    - E/I "Housing Horrors" excerpt transcripts. Project Ya Basta
    - E/I Ya Basta - project description and form, 1974
    - Ya Basta misc. materials
    - E/I He's Got a Secret PR
  - Box 7 - "Fair Housing at Its Worst" (10 volumes), Feb. 1974-May 1977
    - E/I "Fair Housing at Its Worst," Report 1 draft, 1974
    - E/I "Fair Housing at Its Worst," Report 2 draft, 1974
    - E/I "Fair Housing at Its Worst," Report 3 draft, 1974
    - E/I "Fair Housing at Its Worst," Report 4 draft, 1974
    - E/I "Fair Housing at Its Worst," Report 5 draft, 1974
    - E/I "Fair Housing at Its Worst," Report 6 draft, 1974
    - E/I "Fair Housing at Its Worst," Report 7 draft, 1974
    - E/I "Fair Housing at Its Worst," Report 8 draft, 1974
    - E/I "Fair Housing at Its Worst," Report 9 draft, 1974
  - Box 8 - Education/Instruccion Lawsuits
    - US vs. Barrows and Wallace, et al, 1974
    - E/I vs Thomas Moore et al
  - Box 9 - Education/Instruccion - Tax Re-Evaluation
    - Assessment, City of Hartford
    - Mean effective tax rate - charts, 1976
    - "Hartford Adjusting for the After-Effects of a Re-evaluation"
    - Boyd Hinds - tax assessment debate - clippings file, 1977
    - California tax evaluation research, 1978
    - E/I differential tax report, US Chamber of Commerce, 1982
  - Box 10 - Redlining Pamphlet Collection
    - Disclosure, 1974-1975
    - Disclosure, 1976-1977
    - Guide to Practice Open Housing law
    - Redlining - report by FNMA, 1976
    - Urban Disinvestment: New Implications for Community Organization, Research and Public Policy
    - Where the Money Is: Mortgage Lending, Los Angeles County
    - Journal of Housing. No. 9, October 1975
    - Insurance Redlining: Profit$ vs. Policyholders
    - Insurance Redlining: Fact Not Fiction
    - Disclosure and neighborhood Reinvestment, 1976
    - Highway Robbery
    - Hartford: fiscal Problems of an Aging City, Vol. 1 Text, 1976
    - Hartford: fiscal Problems of an Aging City, Vol. 1 Exhibits, 1976
    - Economic Interdependence in the Greater Hartford Region - City and Suburbs, 1976
    - Insurance Crisis in Urban America
  - Box 11 - Insurance Redlining
    - Insurance investigation - exhibits, correspondence
    - Redlining - Insurance, 1977
    - E/I insurance investigation transcript - New London County Mutual
    - E/I insurance investigation transcript - Nationwide
    - E/I insurance investigation transcript - Aetna
    - E/I insurance investigation transcript - Travelers
    - E/I insurance investigation transcript - The Hartford
    - Notes on insurance company's responses to redlining complaint, 1978
    - Insurance underwriting study - final copy, 1979
    - Redlining - insurance ration - research and corr., 1979
    - Insurance readjustment, 1980
  - Box 12 - Education Reform
    - Education equality bill materials, 1975
    - Board of Ed. legislative proposals, 1977
    - Board of Education materials, 1977
    - Board of Ed. transportation complaints, 1978
    - Education/Instruction Inc. - revenue sharing complaints vs. Board of Ed., 1981
    - Ad hoc task force for quality education through integration, 1981
    - Education affirmative action, 1977-1984
  - Box 13 - E/I Banking
    - Banking for Non-bankers, 1977
    - Clippings - banking and housing reform
    - The American Banker, 1977
  - Box 14 - E/I Affirmative Action
    - E/I regional affirmative action correspondence
    - Status of Affirmative Action in Connecticut State Government - report, 1981
    - Desegregation lawsuit materials, 1982
    - CT Commission on Human Rights and Opportunities, 1981
    - Connecticut Allied Business Legal Rights Assoc. affirmative action lawsuit, 1982
    - National Minority Purchasing Council, 1980
  - Box 15 - E/I Employment Resources
    - Employment for district - Department of Commerce
    - Employment discrimination cases
    - E/I proposal for a resource recovery operation, 1978
    - Black Family Institute for Policy and Advancement
  - Box 16 - The Everywhere School
    - Position statements: The Everywhere School
    - Alfred Boyd Hinds, Jr., "Administering the Development, Proposal Writing and Presentation of the South Arsenal Everywhere School to the Hartford Board of Education." MA thesis, Trinity College, 1970
  - Box 17 - The Everywhere School (2)
    - The Everywhere School - project recommendations, 1971
    - The Everywhere School 1 of 2
    - The Everywhere School 2 of 2
  - Box 18 - South Arsenal Development Project Records
    - South Arsenal Development Project to-do (1 of 2)
    - South Arsenal Development Project to-do (2 of 2)
  - Box 19 - Ben Dixon Ph.D. Dissertation in Education 1977
    - Ben Dixon, "Facilitating Citizen Participation in Educational Decision Making Through an Iterative Assessment of Citizen Opinion," UMASS, 1977
    - Ben Dixon, "Facilitating Citizen Participation in Educational Decision Making Through an Iterative Assessment of Citizen Opinion," UMASS (copy 2), 1977
    - Ben Dixon, "Facilitating Citizen Participation in Educational Decision Making Through an Iterative Assessment of Citizen Opinion," UMASS (copy 3), 1977
  - Box 20 - E/I Publicity Materials - Assorted
    - E/I assorted promotional materials - institutional white racism
    - E/I shareholder initiatives - clippings and correspondence, 1976
    - E/I National Peoples Action misc., 1976
    - Stan Shaw, Jeffrey Bensky, Benjamin Dixon. "Stress and Burnout: a Primer for Special Education and Special Services Personnel"
    - "Nuts and Bolts: How to Organize and Finance an Inservice Training Program"
    - "How to Organize an Inservice Training Program"
    - "Preventing Burnout Among Social Service Personnel" - slides
  - Box 21 - E/I internal records
    - E/I Financials, 1978
    - E/I internal memos and correspondence
    - E/I financials - utilities, 1976
    - E/I financials - financial reports, gifts, tax returns
    - E/I correspondence
    - E/I board meeting minutes
    - E/I bylaws
    - E/I discrimination dispute with Patrick Hare
    - Reinstatement and financials C/O Ben Dixon
  - E/I publicity materials - oversize
  - E/I cassette tapes (3 boxes)
- Series II: Political Career
  - Box 22 - Boyd Hinds Campaign, 1976
    - 1976 absentee ballot log
    - Campaign materials - original
    - Advertisements - photo negative slides, 1976
    - Boyd Hinds campaign materials, 1976
    - Campaign materials, 1976
    - Rev. Herb Smith - 1976 election
    - Voter registration - statistics with Boyd Hinds notes, 1976
    - Voter analysis - Boyd campaign 1976 election
    - Flyer (rename campaign promotional materials) - includes photos
    - Untitled folder - misc. campaign materials - Democratic assembly election in city of Hartford
    - Reading materials, 1976
    - Hartford voting districts
    - Committee to re-elect Ella Grasso (77-78)
    - 8th assembly district organization
  - Box 23 - Boyd Hinds Campaign, 1978
    - Hartford city maps, 1977
    - Voter estimates and reports (Hinds campaign), 1978
    - Boyd Hinds campaign ads and endorsements, 1978
    - Primay day transportation, Sept. 1978
    - Self endorsement complaint, 1978
    - Democratic Town Committee records, 1978-1979
    - Halapin campaign information, 1978
    - Flyer (rename campaign promotional materials) - includes photos
    - Untitled folder - performance research on fellow assemlyman, 1977-1978
    - Primary Day transportation, Sept. 1978
  - Box 24 - Boyd Hinds Campaign, 1978 (2)
    - City priorities (20% welfare, pilot program, bilingual policies, taxes moderate rental housing, welfare takeover), 1977
      - 1977 budget surplus appropriations
      - 1977 Boyd Hinds redlining report materials - Urban Planning Caucus
      - 1977 grants in lieu of taxes in state owned property
      - Bilingual Act - CT House of Representatives, 1977
      - 1977 GTB funding appropriations
  - Box 25 - Boyd Hinds Assembly Legislation Record 1
    - H.B. No. 5600 - An Act Concerning Real Estate Appraisal Practices, 1977
    - Senate Bill No. 336 - 1978 - An Act Concerning Residency of Schoolteachers
    - H.B. No. 5878 - An Act Concerning the Real Estate Commission, 1977
    - H.B. No. 5773 - An Act Concerning the the Est. of a State owned Bank, 1977
    - State-owned bank research
    - H.B. No. 5600 - An Act Concerning Real Estate Appraisal Practices, 1977
    - Sen. No. 27 - An Act Requiring Public Disclosure of the Economic Interests of Members of the General Assembly, 1977
    - Sen. No. 59 - "Quits" and "Fire" Labor Practices, 1977
    - Sen. No 124 - An Act Concerning an Office of Small Business Affairs
    - Sen. Bill No. 128, 1977
    - Committee Bill 175 (1977) Tax Exemptions on Solar Panels
    - Sen. Bill 176 Tax Exemptions for Solar System Collectors, 1977
    - H.B. No. 7325 - An Act Concerning Extending the Statute of Limitations on Paternity Proceedings
    - Senate bill 328: An Act Concerning the State Personal Data Act, 1979
    - Civil Center Bill, 1978
    - CT Clean Indoor Air Act, 1979
  - Box 26 - Boyd Hinds Assembly Legislation Record 2
    - Sen. Bill No. 347 - Affirmative Action Plan Filing Requirement, 1977
    - Sen. Bill No. 420 - Weight Limits for Truckers
    - Sen. Bill 486
    - Sen. Bill No. 504 - State Payments to Hospitals, Nursing Homes, Institutions, etc., 1977
    - Sen. Bill No. 569 - Special Ed. Compensation, 1977
    - Sen. Bill No. 918 - An Act for Full Reimbursement for Tax Abatement for Low and Moderate Income Housing, 1977
    - Sen. Bill No. 582 - Elderly Housing, 1977
    - Sen. No. 583 - Relocation Assistance, 1977
    - Sen. No 609 - An Act to Raise the Age of Majority
    - Sen. Bill No. 829 - An Act to Est. a Pilot Program for Shelter Services for Abuse Victims
    - Senate Bill No. 920 Bilingual Education
    - Sen. Bill 958 Family Abuse Law
    - Sen. Bill 968 Code Enforcement
    - Comm. Bill 978 Insurance Rates
    - Sen. Bill 1036
    - Sen. Bill 1072
    - Sen. Bill 1127
    - Sen. Bill 1399 Anti-Redlining Banks - An Act to Prohibit Discrimination in Mortgage Lending
    - HR 1464 Building Code
    - Sen. Bill 1569
    - Sen. Bill 1601
    - Sen. Bill 1651 - Guidelines for Commission on Hosp. and Health Care
    - Sen. Bill 5011
  - Box 27 - Boyd Hinds Assembly Legislation Record 3
    - Sen. Bill No. 5025
    - Bill No. 5049
    - H.B. 6964
    - Comm. Bill No. 5069
    - H.B. No. 5093
    - Comm. Bill No. 5096
    - Comm. Bill No. 5134
    - H.B. No. 5178
    - Comm. Bill No. 5196
    - H.B. 5221
    - H.B. No. 5296
    - Comm. Bill No. 5196
    - H.B. 5221
    - H.B. 5296
    - Comm. Bill No. 5305
    - H.B. 5320
    - Comm. Bill No. 5332
    - Comm. Bill No. 5354
    - H.B. No. 5420
    - H.B. No. 5464
    - H.B. No. 5539
    - H.B. No. 5543
    - H.B. No. 5578
    - H.B. No. 5581
    - H.B. No. 5590
    - H.B. No. 5628
    - H.B. No. 5663
    - H.B. No. 5700
    - H.B. No. 5740
    - H.B. No. 5864
    - H.B. No. 5869
    - H.B. No. 5875
    - H.B. No. 5876
    - H.B. No. 5877
    - H.B. No. 5889
    - H.B. No. 5908 Anti-Sexual Orientation Discrimination Bill
  - Box 28 - Boyd Hinds Assembly Legislation Record 4
    - H.B. No. 5943
    - H.B. No. 5946
    - H.B. No. 5948
    - Comm. Bill No. 1600
    - H.B. No. 6144
    - H.B. No. 6371
    - H.B. No. 6395
    - H.B. No. 6400
    - H.B. No. 6410
    - H.B. No. 6384
    - H.B. No. 6422
    - H.B. No. 6426
    - H.B. No. 6434
    - H.B. No. 6436
    - H.B. No. 6443
    - H.B. No. 6444
    - H.B. No. 6445
    - H.B. No. 6476
    - H.B. No. 6484
    - H.B. No. 6520
    - H.B. No. 6521
    - H.B. No. 6522
    - H.B. No. 6523
    - H.B. No. 6524
    - H.B. No. 6525
    - H.B. No. 6634
    - H.B. No. 6802
    - H.B. No. 6884
    - H.B. No. 6885
    - H.B. No. 7528
    - H.B. No. 7550
    - H.B. No. 7549
    - H.B. No. 7856
  - Box 29 - Boyd Hinds Assembly Legislation Record 5
    - H.B. No. 5480 Payments to Independent Colleges
    - Comm. Bill 8266
    - HB 5480 Payments to Independent Colleges
    - HJR 25 Proposed Resolution of Fair Practices
    - HJ Res. 17 Investment of the State's Long-Term Time Deposit
  - Box 30 - Boyd Hinds Assembly Legislation Record 6
    - HJR 70 Affirmative Action for Seasonal Employment
    - SB 331 An Act Concerning Transportation for the Handicapped and Elderly
    - SB 1180 Increase NHS Funding
    - HJR 25 Proposed Resolution of Fair Practices
    - HB 5001 An Act Concerning Emergency Fuel Needs
    - HB 5006 An Act Eliminating Minority Representation on Board of Ed
    - HB 5076 An Act Concerning the Conversion of the State Armory
    - HB 5182 An Act Concerning the Territorial Rate System for Auto Insurance
    - HB 5141 An Act to Prohibit Oil Providers from Acting as Retail Dealers
    - HB 5230 An Act Requiring Department of Ec. Dev. to est. a Defense Conversion Program
    - HB 5164 An Act Concerning the Hours of Voting at Primaries
    - HB 5328 An Act Concerning the Limitation of State Deposits in Financial Institutions
    - HB 5330 An Act Mandating Affirmative Action Plans for Local and Regional Boards of Ed.
    - HB 5331 An Act Concerning the UCONN Health Center's Program
    - HB 5336 An Act Concerning Exemption of Education Materials from Sales Tax
    - HB 5001 An Act Reducing the Sales Tax to 5 per cent
    - HB 5340 An Act Est. a Circuit Breaker on Property Taxes
    - HB 5343 An Act Increasing the Qualifying Income Level for Elderly Property Tax Relief
    - HB 5344 An Act Limiting Lobbying Activity by Former Legislators
    - HB 5349 An Act Concerning Equal Employment Contract Compliance
    - HB 5351 An Act Est. a Permanent Commission on Spanish-Speaking Opp. in CT
    - HB 5352 An Act Concerning the State Assumption of General Assistance
    - HB 5353 An Act Concerning Group Homes and Halfway Houses
    - HB 5358 An Act Concerning the Real Estate Commission
    - HB 5359 An Act Prohibiting Discrimination Against Families with Children in Apartment Rentals
    - HB 5360 An Act Prohibiting Discrimination Against Welfare Recipients in Apartment Rentals
    - HB 5362 An Act Mandating Affirmative Action Plans for Municipalities
    - HB 5363 An Act Prohibiting Questioning of a Potential Employee about his Arrest Record
    - HB 5364 An Act Concerning Office Space and Staff for Legislators in thir Districts
    - HB 5368 An Act Concerning the Definition of Physically Disabled
    - HB 5369 An Act Est. a Charities Day at Jai Alai Frontons and Dog Tracts
    - HB 5417 An Act Concerning the Selection of Party Endorsed Candidates for Town Committee Members
    - HB 5640 An Act Limiting Community Reinvestment by Financial Investments
    - HB 5645 An Act Concerning Consumer Credit Reporting
    - HB 5853 An Act Concerning Prental Liability for Torts of Minors
    - HB 5877 An Act Concerning State Reimbursement to Towns or Municipalities for Removal of asbestos from School Buildings
    - HB 5885 An Act Concerning Contingent Assurances by Banks or Mortgages
    - HB 5886 An Act Concerning Home Mortgage Disclosure Act
    - HB 5934 An Act Concerning Governmental Divestitures in South Africa
    - HB 5944 An Act Concerning Disclosure of Bids on Residential Real Property be Filed with Town Clerk and be Public Information
    - HB 6362 An Act Concerning Primaries for Election of Town Committee Members and Self-Endorsement by Convention Delegates
    - HB 6369 An Act Concerning Membership of the State Advisory Council on Children and Youth Services
    - HB 6594 An Act Concerning Welfare Benefits
    - HB 6602 An Act Annual Certification of Realtors by the CT Real Estate Commission
  - Box 31 - Boyd Hinds Assembly Legislation Record 7
    - HB 6590 An Act Concerning the Prohibition of Discrimination in the Auto Insurance Rates
    - HB 6596 An Act the State Assumption of General Assistance
    - HB 6667 An Act Concerning Current Funding of the State’s Share of Gen. Asst. Payments
    - HB 6716 Concerning UCONN’s Share of the Maintenance and Operation Cost of Burgdorf Health Center
    - HB 5853 An Act Concerning Liability for Torts of Mirrors
    - HB 6957 Redlining – Against Denying Financing to Banks Funding Residencies with Four or More Families
    - HB 7198 An Act Concerning the Number of Signatures Required on Nominating Petitions
    - HB 7199 An Act Concerning Welfare Benefits
    - HB 7202 An Act Concerning Homeowners Insurance
    - HB 7203 An Act Concerning Victims of Juvenile Crime
    - Draft – An Act Concerning Agreements to Fix Assessments in Rehabilitation Areas
    - HB 7210 – An Act Concerning State Assistance for Small Contractors in Securing Performance Bonds
    - HB 7211 An Act Concerning the Set Aside Program for Small Contractors
    - HB 5367 An Act Concerning Mandatory Affirmative Action Plans in Companies Receiving Assistance from the CT Development Authority
    - S.J. Res. 21 Eliminating the Straight Ticket Levers from Voting Machines
    - H.B. No. 5945
    - H.B. No. 5942
    - H.B. No. 5941
    - H.B. No. 5679
    - H.B. No. 5587 Anti-Redlining
    - H.B. No. 5527
    - H.B. No. 5528
    - H.B. 5071 Chronic Crooks Act
    - Sen. Bill. No. 357 – Reorganization of the Executive Branch of State Government, 1977
    - H.B. No. 5526 – An Act Concerning Community Reinvestments by Financial Investments, 1977
    - Senate Bill No. 57 Employment Opportunities Program
    - Open Line, 1977
    - Equal Credit Opportunity Act
  - Box 32 - Boyd Hinds--Legislative Records--Bill Drafts (1)
    - Bills proposed by Hinds, 1979
    - Boyd Hinds co-sign bills, 1979
    - Draft bills - election law reform, 1979
    - Draft bill - hospital cost
    - Bills discussed at Jan. 1977 hearing
    - Legislative sessions, 1977
    - CT General Assembly legislative review drafts, 1977
  - Box 33 - Boyd Hinds--Legislative Records--Bill Drafts (2)
    - Letters on bills, 1976-1978
    - Voting project - copies
    - Public endorsements - organizations
    - No vote roll call data
    - 1977-1978 session roll call votes
    - CT Assembly patronage laws (called abe and clyde)